Aditi Dass

aditid@bu.edu +1 (857)-272-1725 github.com/aditid linkedin.com/in/aditidass/

Summary

Recent Masters in Computer Science graduate. 1+ year cumulative experience in full-stack development and applied cryptography. Adept and adaptive learner - previous internship involved different stacks for each new project. Enthusiastic researcher and contributor of digital decentralized systems.

Technical Profile

Languages Python, JavaScript, C, C#, Java, C++, GoLang Back End Node.js, AJAX, SQL, MySQL, MongoDB, PHP

APIs Javax. Crypto, PyCrypto, TensorFlow, Binance, Quantopian

Web Design HTML, CSS, JavaScript, D3.js

Experience

Software Application and Innovation Lab, Hariri Institute of Computing **Boston** Software Developer and Research Intern

May 2017 - Aug 2017

- Designed a cryptographic protocol for privacy preserving data aggregation that was adopted by a NIH funded healthcare firm
- Co-managed project to transition backend framework from Java to JavaScript
- Developed AJAX API routes and models for \$1M funded synthetic biological tool
- · Implemented algorithm in C# for an untrusted, anonymous digital coin tumbler

Software Developer Intern

May 2016 - Jul 2016

- Assessed several open source backend frameworks based on individual project requirements
- · Built accessible adaptive survey platform with Node.js frameworks and Ionic

Boston University Venture Accelerator, BUZZ Lab

Boston

Technology Director

Sep 2016 - May 2017

- · Led consultations for startups' website/app development and advised on tech hiring decisions
- · Worked with non-technical clients where software had to be illustrated across interdisciplinary fields

Project Manager

Sep 2015 - May 2016

 Mentored multiple startups at conception phase in financial modeling and scaling to pitch successfully to investors

Outreach

Codebreakers 2016, LERNet

Boston

Undergraduate Coordinator

Jul 2016 - Aug 2016

- · Designed and developed teaching material and agenda for summer program
- · Introduced female high schoolers to Python with a focus on cryptography and network security

Education

Boston University

Boston

BA/MS in Computer Science, Minor in Mechanical Engineering

Sep 2013 - Dec 2017

 Relevant Coursework: Machine Learning, Distributed Systems, Network Security, Applied Cryptography, Advanced Algorithms, Computer Networks, Software Engineering